https://www.1x2monster.com/privacy-statement/

1x2monsterPerformanceFootyforecast PerformanceRateform PerformanceWin Draw Loss PerformanceSimple Sequence PerformanceScore Prediction PerformanceBest PerformanceSuperform PerformanceLive ScoresBlogHelpContact Us1X2Monster SitemapPrivacy StatementLegal Statement
1X2Monster Privacy Statement - 1X2Monster.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: 1X2Monster.com.LINKS TO EXTERNAL SITESThis site may contain links to other sites. 1X2Monster.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.ADVERTISEMENTSSome of our advertising partners may deliver a cookie to better track ad impressions and click rates. We also use cookies to track login information for affiliated members when they are administering their accounts.COOKIESA cookie is a small data file that certain web sites write to your hard drive when you visit them. A cookie file can contain information such as a user ID that the site uses to track the pages you've visited. But the only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie can't read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites.You can refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser. You and your visitors do not need to have cookies turned on to use the 1X2Monster.com content. However, you will need them turned on when administering your account as we use them to ensure the security of your account.MAILING LISTSWhen you join this site you will be added to our mailing list.The following section applies to all mailing lists associated with 1X2Monster.comPersonal information is never passed or sold to third parties for marketing or solicitation purposes.We may elect to use a third party to help us with the distribution of our emails/newsletters. However, this will be with the understanding that any third party keeps any information secure and uses it solely for the purpose of distributing our newsletter containing our content. Any such third party would be bound by our privacy policy with regard to the use of our membership list.From time to time you may receive an email from us containing an offer we feel you may be interested in from one of our advertising partners - Although this may not be in the form of one of our newsletters the mailing will be distributed by us without access to our subscriber list being passed to our advertising partners.PERSONAL INFORMATIONYour name, email address and any other information you may supply to us, and that of your visitors that they may share through our various signup processes, are never passed on to third parties unless you or your visitors specifically request to be added to third party lists though their designated signup process.From time to time some of our advertising partners may prompt you or your visitor to enter your email address or other personal information via an ad on this site. Please refer to their privacy policy for their specific use of this information.YOUR IP ADDRESSFrom time to time we may need to use your IP address or that of your visitor to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site.If you have any further questions on this statement please contact us through the support pages.Thank you. 1X2Monster
Australian AAus BunBel ProDen SupEng PremierEng ChampEng Leag OneEng Leag TwoEng NationalEng Nat NorthEng Nat SouthFin VeikkausliigaFrance Ligue 1Ger BundesligaGre Super LigItaly Serie ANet EredivisieNor TippeligaenPor Prim LigaRus PremierSco PremierSco ChampSco Leag OneSco Leag TwoSpain La LigaSwe AllsvenskanTur Super Lig
Sources: Arsenal squad hold clear-the-air talks
on December 4, 2020 at 7:34 pm Arsenal's players exchanged angry words with each […]
Sources: PSG exploring summer move for Messi
on December 4, 2020 at 7:34 pm Messi's contract expires at the end of the season […]
Napoli's stadium renamed after Diego Maradona
on December 4, 2020 at 7:34 pm Italian side Napoli's San Paolo stadium has been […]
FIFA approves maternity leave for players
on December 4, 2020 at 7:34 pm Professional women footballers are to be […]
Juventus investigated over Suarez citizenship test
on December 4, 2020 at 7:34 pm Juventus are under investigation following […]
ENGLISH PREMIERSHIP#TeamPlWDLPts1 Manchester City 12 10 2 0 32 2 Liverpool 12 9 3 0 30 3 Chelsea 12 8 4 0 28 4 Tottenham Hotsp 12 9 0 3 27 5 Arsenal 12 7 3 2 24 6 Afc Bournemouth 12 6 2 4 20 7 Watford 12 6 2 4 20 8 Manchester Unit 12 6 2 4 20 9 Everton 12 5 4 3 19 10 Leicester City 12 5 2 5 17 11 Woverhampton Wa 12 4 4 4 16 12 Brighton & Hove 12 4 2 6 14 13 West Ham United 12 3 3 6 12 14 Newcastle Unite 12 2 3 7 9 15 Burnley 12 2 3 7 9 16 Crystal Palace 12 2 2 8 8 17 Southampton 12 1 5 6 8 18 Cardiff City 12 2 2 8 8 19 Huddersfield To 12 1 4 7 7 20 Fulham 12 1 2 9 5 Last Updated: 15th November 2018Latest NewsLatest PostsScore Prediction – Soccer Statistical MethodBy Editorial StaffMarch 18, 2018Score Prediction for football (soccer) games is highly
[…]What is the Footyforecast Statistical Method?By Editorial StaffMay 12, 2016The Footyforecast method was originally developed for
[…]Rateform – Soccer Statistical MethodBy Editorial StaffJanuary 23, 2016Rateform has its origins in The Rating Of Chessplayers
[…]
